olwomen.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | OLWomen.com

### Purpose of the Privacy Policy:

The main purpose of this privacy policy is to ensure the readers that how this website will treat your personal information. All the Personally Identifiable Information is gathered when you visit this website through your mobile phone or personal computer. If you register through this site or send any of personal your data through Contact Us, all these registration and services are free of cost.

Whenever you use our services, we automatically save your personal data on the device you use, along with operating system version, device identifier and mobile carriers. All this information is collected for the purpose of optimization that how you use this application. Be careful while posting your information, any incorrect, outdated and false information will stop you from the registration process of OlWomen.com.

### Internet Traffic and OlWomen.com:

Whenever you use the amazing services and products of OlWomen.com, this site may collect some important information such as page impressions, session duration, mobile carriers, IP addresses, domain name that you have used to access the services, origins and content types. All these information is used to control the internet traffic on the website.

### Do We Collect Location Based Information?

OlWomen.com is not at all interested in collecting your personal data based on your geographical location. It will just look for the country you are residing in when you were using its services, even when the services are not at all active. Some of the location based information might be stored on the OlWomen.com server when the visitor wants to use the geographically based services. All this information will be discarded as it is no longer in use.

### What Do We Do With Your Personally Identifiable Information?

OlWomen.com will use your personally identifiable information for the following reasons:

  * To operate and provide website services.
  * If our website will be offering some services for a fee, then all the payment information will be stored, saved and used.
  * To send you notices and latest updates and information related to new services.
  * To contact you whenever it is required.
  * To prevent any sort of fraud and identity theft.
  * To collect services fees and debts.

### Children’s Policy:

Children under the age of 13 are not intended to use any of the information and services from the website. If you are 13 or older, in that case you are allowed according to the website policies to use any of the information and services of OlWomen.com. Kindly refrain from providing any of your personal information and we do not collect any information from people under 13 years.

### Do We Share your Personally Identified Information with Others?

OlWomen.com does not lease, sell or rent any of your Personally Identified Information with any type of third party. Some information might be shared in case of the following instances:

  * To operate some site services.
  * To contact you in any emergency.
  * If by law it is required to share your personal information, then our website will take a certain step.
  * In case of any kind of legal proceedings.
  * To prevent any kind of imminent damage or harm.
  * To the companies or websites connected to OlWomen.com.

### How Can You Get An Access To Your Personal Information?

If you have registered with our website and to different services, you can access your personal information and also you will have the facility to edit and update your information. If you are not able to edit, update or delete any of your information, then you can contact us through our email address _**olwomen1@gmail.com**_. We will try to reach you as soon as possible.

### Is Your Personal Information Secured with OlWomen.com?

OlWomen.com and any of it related websites are responsible for the security of all your personal information. They have special procedures and system to secure your data. These systems reduce the information theft, but they do not provide absolute security. OlWomen.com cannot guarantee any of the malfunctions or unlawful interceptions that may happen.

### What about links to Third Party Website?

Our website carries links to some third party websites that are not owned by us. For your notice, kindly be aware that we are not at all responsible for the privacy policies of the third party. We encourage you to stay alert and whatever dealing you will be doing with them, it will not be our responsibility.

### Changes in our Privacy Policy:

Our privacy policy statements are subject to change. We have the right to change any of the privacy policies anytime and anywhere we want. Any changes made will be notified to the registered users through email or by means of a special notice on the website. We encourage you to keep visiting the site in order to stay updated with the latest information.
